[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 34, "question": "I'm like, I am so lost -- you know what I was thinking, can I be very funny for a minute?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "like", ",", "I", "am", "so", "lost", "--", "you", "know", "what", "I", "was", "thinking", ",", "can", "I", "be", "very", "funny", "for", "a", "minute", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 35, "answer": "Yes, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "And I'm going sitting here looking over at Trump, and I'm thinking, he started with her, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "I", "'m", "going", "sitting", "here", "looking", "over", "at", "Trump", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "thinking", ",", "he", "started", "with", "her", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBG", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "Like he has a pattern, right?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "he", "has", "a", "pattern", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "He does.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "does", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 51, "question": "Was it the same for you?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "the", "same", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 52, "answer": "Period.", "answer_tokens": ["Period", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Of course, every time you're absolute end.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", ",", "every", "time", "you", "'re", "absolute", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RB", "POS", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Did you ever find out there's any link between the injury you suffered there?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "find", "out", "there", "'s", "any", "link", "between", "the", "injury", "you", "suffered", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "I don't think anyone -- I don't anyone is going to be able to physically go here's there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "anyone", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "anyone", "is", "going", "to", "be", "able", "to", "physically", "go", "here", "'s", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Did you have any idea what this was -- what was going on, what was happening to you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "any", "idea", "what", "this", "was", "--", "what", "was", "going", "on", ",", "what", "was", "happening", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "DT", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Did you think then that you may die?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "think", "then", "that", "you", "may", "die", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "I'll be honest with you at that moment I -- I didn't even think about anything but getting to the emergency room.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ll", "be", "honest", "with", "you", "at", "that", "moment", "I", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "even", "think", "about", "anything", "but", "getting", "to", "the", "emergency", "room", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Were they confiding in you about this or was it something your family told you later?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "they", "confiding", "in", "you", "about", "this", "or", "was", "it", "something", "your", "family", "told", "you", "later", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "No, they -- about three days -- after they knew -- when I went in the emergency room the night it happened they -- you know I was telling them, I don't care if you got to saw my head open, do whatever you go to do, I want to live.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "--", "about", "three", "days", "--", "after", "they", "knew", "--", "when", "I", "went", "in", "the", "emergency", "room", "the", "night", "it", "happened", "they", "--", "you", "know", "I", "was", "telling", "them", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "care", "if", "you", "got", "to", "saw", "my", "head", "open", ",", "do", "whatever", "you", "go", "to", "do", ",", "I", "want", "to", "live", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "CD", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "What was that moment hike?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "moment", "hike", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "That was the strangest moment because I opened my eyes and there was about six or seven, maybe eight people and they have these things on your legs to keep the blood, you know, the blood flowing so people were like working on your legs and they're -- they were doing stuff with my hands.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "the", "strangest", "moment", "because", "I", "opened", "my", "eyes", "and", "there", "was", "about", "six", "or", "seven", ",", "maybe", "eight", "people", "and", "they", "have", "these", "things", "on", "your", "legs", "to", "keep", "the", "blood", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "blood", "flowing", "so", "people", "were", "like", "working", "on", "your", "legs", "and", "they", "'re", "--", "they", "were", "doing", "stuff", "with", "my", "hands", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "How did they deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "they", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "At first, you know -- again, my first 12 days I don't really remember much and I think they had a tough time at first and then as -- they know I'm a fighter so they know once I made it through that the first initial 10 days is the fighting, is the real scary period.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "first", ",", "you", "know", "--", "again", ",", "my", "first", "12", "days", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "remember", "much", "and", "I", "think", "they", "had", "a", "tough", "time", "at", "first", "and", "then", "as", "--", "they", "know", "I", "'m", "a", "fighter", "so", "they", "know", "once", "I", "made", "it", "through", "that", "the", "first", "initial", "10", "days", "is", "the", "fighting", ",", "is", "the", "real", "scary", "period", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 214, "question": "You know what I mean?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "I", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "You were to become forever the guy who died watching \"Busty Cops 3.\"", "answer_tokens": ["You", "were", "to", "become", "forever", "the", "guy", "who", "died", "watching", "``", "Busty", "Cops", "3", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "Can it happen to anyone at any time?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "it", "happen", "to", "anyone", "at", "any", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "The scariest thing about this form of hemorrhage, there -- you know, that's different from a brain tumor or even in an instance it's like a brain aneurysm.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "scariest", "thing", "about", "this", "form", "of", "hemorrhage", ",", "there", "--", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "different", "from", "a", "brain", "tumor", "or", "even", "in", "an", "instance", "it", "'s", "like", "a", "brain", "aneurysm", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Were you not thinking, what have I done to deserve all this?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "not", "thinking", ",", "what", "have", "I", "done", "to", "deserve", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "First day, you know, when you ask me, first I'm thinking, before I felt like what did I do to deserve this, because I've done a lot of stuff to deserve it.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "day", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "you", "ask", "me", ",", "first", "I", "'m", "thinking", ",", "before", "I", "felt", "like", "what", "did", "I", "do", "to", "deserve", "this", ",", "because", "I", "'ve", "done", "a", "lot", "of", "stuff", "to", "deserve", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "You've been a diabetic how long?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "a", "diabetic", "how", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "WRB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "Since I've been 6 years old, and I'm 47 now, so a long time.", "answer_tokens": ["Since", "I", "'ve", "been", "6", "years", "old", ",", "and", "I", "'m", "47", "now", ",", "so", "a", "long", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "And in absolute simple practical terms, what do you need to do to yourself every day as a diabetic?", "question_tokens": ["And", "in", "absolute", "simple", "practical", "terms", ",", "what", "do", "you", "need", "to", "do", "to", "yourself", "every", "day", "as", "a", "diabetic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Well, here's what it is, I now was saying this during the break and I was laughing hard because it was like the Tonys, I said man, I possibly need to check my blood, I'm dying.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "here", "'s", "what", "it", "is", ",", "I", "now", "was", "saying", "this", "during", "the", "break", "and", "I", "was", "laughing", "hard", "because", "it", "was", "like", "the", "Tonys", ",", "I", "said", "man", ",", "I", "possibly", "need", "to", "check", "my", "blood", ",", "I", "'m", "dying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Every day?", "question_tokens": ["Every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Yes, because I've had it so long.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "I", "'ve", "had", "it", "so", "long", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "VBZ", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "You are about to now just check what, exactly?", "question_tokens": ["You", "are", "about", "to", "now", "just", "check", "what", ",", "exactly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "WP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "All this is -- all this does is check my blood because the old way, why a lot of diabetics got sick is -- when you would test your urine, it could be from the night before.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "this", "is", "--", "all", "this", "does", "is", "check", "my", "blood", "because", "the", "old", "way", ",", "why", "a", "lot", "of", "diabetics", "got", "sick", "is", "--", "when", "you", "would", "test", "your", "urine", ",", "it", "could", "be", "from", "the", "night", "before", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "You just pop your finger, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "just", "pop", "your", "finger", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "And if you get a bad result, what do you need to do?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "get", "a", "bad", "result", ",", "what", "do", "you", "need", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, my result right now is 119 which is really good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "result", "right", "now", "is", "119", "which", "is", "really", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "It's a lifelong balance, right?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "lifelong", "balance", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "What sort of memory does that bring back that moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "sort", "of", "memory", "does", "that", "bring", "back", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "You know, for me very, very painful and I say it for this reason.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "for", "me", "very", ",", "very", "painful", "and", "I", "say", "it", "for", "this", "reason", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What's happened to Raine since then?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "happened", "to", "Raine", "since", "then", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "She's pre-diabetic.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "pre-diabetic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Raine"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Do you worry about it all at time?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "worry", "about", "it", "all", "at", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Yeah, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Are you involved in that?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "involved", "in", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Let me explain what happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "explain", "what", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "So you've been quite smart protecting yourself?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "'ve", "been", "quite", "smart", "protecting", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Very.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bobby", "Ricky"]}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "You made sure you got the money you should have got?", "question_tokens": ["You", "made", "sure", "you", "got", "the", "money", "you", "should", "have", "got", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "Here's where it is -- with our band, I give this credit to Bobby and Ricky and CC growing up together.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "where", "it", "is", "--", "with", "our", "band", ",", "I", "give", "this", "credit", "to", "Bobby", "and", "Ricky", "and", "CC", "growing", "up", "together", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Can you still be as wild as you used to be?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "still", "be", "as", "wild", "as", "you", "used", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Coming to one awesome part of your back catalog, which is is it now obligatory to enter a certain very special rock star club, that you have had to made a sex tape with Pamela Anderson?", "question_tokens": ["Coming", "to", "one", "awesome", "part", "of", "your", "back", "catalog", ",", "which", "is", "is", "it", "now", "obligatory", "to", "enter", "a", "certain", "very", "special", "rock", "star", "club", ",", "that", "you", "have", "had", "to", "made", "a", "sex", "tape", "with", "Pamela", "Anderson", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Apparently it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Apparently", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Pamela Anderson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Got a wedding date yet?", "question_tokens": ["Got", "a", "wedding", "date", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "We haven't.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "have", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["New York Dolls"]}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Who is the special guest though?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "the", "special", "guest", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "The New York Dolls.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "New", "York", "Dolls", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Who is going to win?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "is", "going", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "I got to say we're going to win, come on.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "got", "to", "say", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "win", ",", "come", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Wednesday"]}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "What am I doing in this hell hole?", "question_tokens": ["What", "am", "I", "doing", "in", "this", "hell", "hole", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "That was a Wednesday.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "a", "Wednesday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "When do tickets go on sale?", "question_tokens": ["When", "do", "tickets", "go", "on", "sale", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Here's what it is: Motley Crue, Poison, New York Dolls and special guest, SS.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "what", "it", "is", ":", "Motley", "Crue", ",", "Poison", ",", "New", "York", "Dolls", "and", "special", "guest", ",", "SS", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Is that the greatest kick you have?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "greatest", "kick", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Professionally, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Professionally", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "If I could tell you, here's the deal: you can either have sex for the rest of your life or perform on stage, you can't do both, which one do you take?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "tell", "you", ",", "here", "'s", "the", "deal", ":", "you", "can", "either", "have", "sex", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "or", "perform", "on", "stage", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "do", "both", ",", "which", "one", "do", "you", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ",", "WDT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Both.", "answer_tokens": ["Both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "Is this like Sophie's choice?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "like", "Sophie", "'s", "choice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sophie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "''", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 687, "question": "Which way are you going to go?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "way", "are", "you", "going", "to", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 688, "answer": "I'm going to have to go with the rock 'n' roll, and here's why, because it will bring me sex.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "have", "to", "go", "with", "the", "rock", "'n", "'", "roll", ",", "and", "here", "'s", "why", ",", "because", "it", "will", "bring", "me", "sex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "Does he need help, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "need", "help", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "We all need help.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "all", "need", "help", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "What's the simple quick fix for Charlie?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "simple", "quick", "fix", "for", "Charlie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "I don't think there is one.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "there", "is", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Does part of you worry that if Charlie is not careful that it could cost him his life?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "part", "of", "you", "worry", "that", "if", "Charlie", "is", "not", "careful", "that", "it", "could", "cost", "him", "his", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110302pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "You mean the new one?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "the", "new", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "ORGAN: Seriously.", "answer_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Seriously", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]